Shruti Khandekar

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Highly motivated recent graduate with Advanced Certificate in Web and Mobile Application Development (GPA of 3.26), with many years of prior experience as Sr. Quality Assurance Engineer at large companies. Mature and dedicated professional with training in design principles and programming languages, seeking opportunity in Web Application Development and Testing.

Education

Advanced Certificate in Web And Mobile Application, San Diego State University, San Diego

JULY 2018 - MAY 2020

Bachelor of Engineering, Pune University, Pune, India

JUNE 1999 - AUGUST 2002

Instrumentation Engineering

Projects

JULY 2018 - MAY 2020

Product Inventory

Used MERN stack to create a full-stack product Inventory application. Displayed knowledge in CRUD (Create, Update, Delete) operations. Pull in data from the MongoDB server and display inventory in tabulated format on an SPA using ReactJS. Used Express in the back-end. Added routing for the Single Page App using React-router.

Corporate website

Created a four-page website for a sample corporation using MERN stack. The website included web pages for Home, About Us, Solutions, and Contact Us. Added Grid layouts and used SASS for styling the webpage.

Employee Management System

Built an Employee Management application that allowed the user to show all employees, add an employee, and delete an employee. Used multi-dimensional data to persist employee data.

Employment History

Sr Software Quality Assurance Specialist, Oracle Corp, Los Angeles

MARCH 2010 - JULY 2012

Worked on creating frameworks for both client and server-side test automation for Oracle SOA suite. Worked as part of scrum team, for product development for upcoming releases of Oracle SOA product.

Programmatic Automation Engineer, Sun Microsystems, Los Angeles

DECEMBER 2003 - FEBRUARY 2010

Created manual tests and automated test harness for both web-based and client-server based java application which ran successfully on all windows, Linux and Unix platforms.

Details

10513 Sand Crab Place, San Diego, 92130, United States 8589268476 shrutikhandekar1@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

Skills

JavaScript

HTML5/CSS3

ReactJS

Java

Express/NodeJS

Ajax

GitHub

MongoDB/SQL

Windows 2000/NT/XP, Solaris SPARC, Linux and UNIX